Deja View Film Eyebrow Color
Aquos Q&A
I want to take nice portraits.
Aquos is a large camera, so it's good at portraits.
That's nice!
A big camera!
Here's the real thing!
Softbank Aquos R8 PRO Campaign
Only those who want to drink All Free from the bottom of their heart can pass through this gate!
Go ahead.
Which one is this?
Welcome to Suntory All Free!
Nikon is more than just cameras
Nikon is not just about cameras.
We support society through various innovations.
Transcending the Impossible with the Power of Light
The possibilities are endless Nikon
This Wonderful World will start on Thursday, July 20th at 10:00 p.m.
Master, Año Haseyo!
So, I'm here for the first time overseas!
Not overseas, not overseas.
Año haseyo!
No, no, no.
Shin-Okubo.
What, Shin-Okubo?
Japanese is more common here.
That's why you didn't need a passport.
So that's how it is.
You can't go on location.
And you can enjoy yourself with the master.
We have Harapeko guests here.We have guests from Harapeko!
Here they are!
Año haseyo!
We have a new genre of music!
Here we are again, Hanaho Kobayashi, who plays the role of Shrity Bish.
and Yuna Kokubo, who will be playing the role of Shrity Bish. Please give us your best regards.
Good morning.
You must be number 11 and 14.
Yes, number 11 and 14.
Great.
From the eternal junior high idols, Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
From Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku, the eternal idols of junior high school.
They've come in hungry.
Po-chan and...
I'm Yunobi.
Po-chan and Yunobi?
Yes, that's right.
I can call them that? Is that...
Po-chan is from Saitama Prefecture.
Yes, he's a good worker, just like Asato.
Asato.
Asato's active, but this one's...
You're with Crayon Shin-chan
That's right.
You can do it, too, Crayon Shin-chan?
Nanako!
You can do it!
Isn't she good?
Not many idols can do it this well.
There are a lot of them.There's quite a lot of them.
How embarrassing!
I, Yunobi, am from Aichi Prefecture, so...
Mr. Takada.
That's right, I do this program here in the Tokai area.
I see.
So you are from your hometown?
That's right.
Then may I see Crayon Shin-chan?
Sure, sure.
Nanako.
Oh!
You look like him.
Well then, let's go
With these two... here's the oil theme we're going to enjoy this time.
I like oil, so I'm going to eat Korean Village and have some Yebisu!
Yay!
It's going to make everyone smile.
That's right, Korean gourmet food popular among young people
Korean Town Shin-Okubo to inoculate your body
We're going to make you smile!
It's a great episode!
Let's go to the first restaurant!
Yay!
Let's start the food terror show that brings you oil and energy!
The Gourmet Magic of the Harapeko Majin Oil Shoulder Bra
This broadcast is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching!
Shin-Okubo, the holy land of Korean gourmet food!
You'll be smiling with a smile on your Ebisu face after eating a lot of oil!
ArrivalArrival
If you come first, here is Koruboki Shokudo!
The first restaurant?
Yes, here we are!
I've never seen an opening this close to the restaurant.
It says "opening" on the menu.
Opening time?
Basically, this is the place to shoot the opening!
Here we are at Kolmoku Shokudo, a popular restaurant with a line up and a reputation for being the best in terms of cost.
Kolmoku Shokudo, a popular restaurant with a long line!
I wonder what kind of kori oil they serve!
The kori oil served here is...
The oil menu is related to the two members of Ebichu!
It's just like an arts and crafts world of oil!
The world of arts and sciences
What arts and crafts world?
What?
I can't believe it!
Ebichu's name means "junior high school", so they call their live performances "Gakugeikai", as if it were an academic world.
You mean live performance?
That's right.
Is that what you mean?
It's common sense.
So you guys are in junior high school?
Yes, real junior high school students.
I'm in the 35th year of junior high school.
Junior high school student.
I'm a family member.
I'm a member of a family?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you fans of Shrimps?What are the fans of Ebichu?
We call our fans the EBICHU family.
That's right.
I want you to know more about us.
And if you haven't had enough chili oil yet...
Let's have a taste now!
Oil or Double Oil
Okay, title, title, title.
Hello, hello.
It's a specialty of this restaurant, isn't it?
Shrimp roll samgyopsal!
Yay!
Looks delicious!
Oily pork belly wrapped around plump shrimp
Grilled until the surface is golden brown
Shrimp roll samgyeopsal is ready!
It's the beginning of the oil school arts and crafts festival!
I heard that there is a finishing touch.
Here is a little burner burner.
Burn it with a burner.
Where?
The shrimp.
They look delicious.
The tails of the shrimp, they're kind of crispy.
That's pretty good.
I can taste it coming.
The cheese has a nice char on it.
Looks delicious!
And there's corn on the cob too!
I wonder if all the members of the shrimp club come to have dinner together.Do all the members of Ebichu come to have dinner together?
In between the live concert.
You said it's a live concert!
The school arts and crafts festival...
I didn't say that!
I didn't say it! I didn't say it!
The day after the arts and crafts, we'll all have dinner together.
That's right.
But it's not easy... because of Corona and all.
But nowadays, we usually go to live shows.
You said "live"!
No, we don't.
No, I haven't.
No, I didn't.
Okay, it's time for lunch.
School lunch! Ready, set, go!
Bon appétit! Pon-chan, you're growing so fast!
It's growing! How far do you want it to go?
It won't cut it!
It's hot... be careful.
How's the cheese?
Yum!
It's delicious.
It's very savory.
Oh, yeah.
Shrimp.
Delicious.
Give me some prawns, prawns, prawns, prawns!
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
So cute!Nice and cute.
Eunobi Eunobi, give it to me.
Bon appétit!
You're good at dipping.
It's delicious.
It's good, it's good, it stretches.
Stretch it, stretch it, stretch it, stretch it, and then ween on top of that.
Eunobis and shrimps are connected.
Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
Nice smile... nice shrimp... real face.
Shivavi is good!
Shibabi!
Shebabi!
Who's there?
Well, well, well.
Oh, it's good.
The shrimp.
A really nice mixture of pork fat.
Yes, yes, yes.
Very fresh.
Fresh.
It's like a first year of deliciousness.
Delicious!
Tortillas and, you know, sandwiches are good, too.
I'd like to try it with a tortilla.
Bon appétit!
Go ahead, go ahead, go ahead.
Oh, wow.
It's totally different.
It's like eating a sandwich.Like eating a sandwich.
Like we're eating sandwiches.
Then it's like, why don't you just have a sandwich?
Tortillas are really good.
It's my first tortilla.
My first tortilla.
It's so good!
Yum!
What do you think?
It's soft!
It's a little bit sticky, but it changes the texture of the tortilla.
The tortilla...
The tortillas are connected to the plumpness of the shrimp.
It's great.
But you know what? There's another kind of collie oil that uses shrimp.
So let's summon it!
oil field bath
Oh, great.
Here we go.
It's snowing!
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's like shaved ice!
Snowy shrimp!
Snowy Shrimp!
Bite-sized shrimp and cheese piled up like a mountain of snow!
Ladies and gentlemen, please wait!
We can't let you eat it for free!
We don't negotiate on region!
The three of you will play a game called "Shrimp Game," not like the popular Korean drama "Squid Game.
The two winners will get a gourmet meal!
And unfortunately, the one who does not win will die.And unfortunately, the one who didn't win died.
Why is that?
The contents of the shrimp game are as follows
This is the all-out shrimp-enemy-enemy self-introduction showdown.
Self-introduction
That's right, the shrimpers have their own unique way of self-introduction.
Yes, we all have our own self-introductions that we can enjoy with our families.
Oh, you do? Everyone has that kind of excitement.
Let's get the moment going with another gourmet prawn dish!
The first two to introduce themselves are Miss My Pace, Miko Yunomiko and Ms. Kunitomo.
I'll ask you in English, and you answer in English.
Understood, sir.
Hello.
I'm a junior high school student
Yuno
I know
I like to go at my own pace. I'm Student Number 14, Kokubu. I'm Yuno. Nice to meet you.
Yay!
The family's going all out. They're going above and beyond. They're going above and beyond.
First of all, Yunomi, right?
You're sweating, Family!
Next, Po-chan...
Okay, let's go.
Next, the ever-smiling Mr. Kobayashi, aka Po-chan.
I want you to say Poe after me, and then Poe for the fourth time.
Poe after me.
Yes, I see.
All right, everyone, let's go!Gentlemen, you can do it!
I can do it!
Are you sure you can do it? - I'm sure I can do it! Are you sure you can do it?
Just a little bit... Just a little bit...
You're too conspicuous. You're too conspicuous.
No, no, no... but we need a little incentive.
They're really hyping it up. They're hyping it up too much.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Face that way, rock-paper-scissors, face this way.
I'm Kaho Kobayashi, number 11.
I'm the family coordinate.
I'm Mazin
And I'm Mazin.
Coordinates Mazin.
You're here!
No, no, no, I'm so excited!
From a family point of view, just seeing you introduce yourself like this...
And the last one to get the prize is...
I'm Shibata-san, the big winner!
I'm going to sing.
Sing? Yes...
Like a call-and-response.
At the end, everyone sings...
We're supposed to say the last word?
Say it at the end.
I'm sure you'll notice.
I see.
Shibatan, let's introduce ourselves.
Yay!
Sing.
Me, me, me, everyone's, everyone's Shibatan, Shibatan, Shibatan, Shibatan, Shibatan, Rock'n!I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, everyone's, Shibatan, Shibatan, Shibatan, Shibatan, Rockin'!
Yes!
Shibata Ron-queue!
Yes, sir.
Make up your mind.
I gave it my all.
It just arrived.
The winner is...
Pon-chan, Irrapee.
Yay!
Ron queue.
Pon-chan Irapy.
Winner.
Europie! Europy! Europy!
Europy! Europy! Europy!
I told you you were the winner.
I'm actually the winner.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry you can't eat.
Yay!
While we were introducing ourselves, the food was ready to eat!
The winners, Ms. Kobayashi and Ms. Kunitomo
Please eat up!
Po-chan Europie! Po-chan Europie!
Let's go!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Wow, it stretches.
It's growing!
It's amazing.That's great.
Bon appétit.
I can't get it off.
Cheese.
Ah, stupid.
Po-chan.
Oh, hot!
There's more family here.
Yum! Is it good?
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum. Yum.
The cheese is different again from the other cheese.
It's different. Is it creamier? It's more creamy.
Creamier. Thank you.
Perope, be careful.
It's good. There's corn in it.
It's got corn in it. It's got corn in it.
There's corn in this.
Yes, there's a little bit of corn, too.
The shrimp is so juicy and the corn is so crunchy, it's delicious.
Good commentary.
That was really good, you two.
Thank you so much!
What's wrong with me?
I couldn't get into it.
That's up to you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Snow was great.
It was delicious.It was delicious.
I'm sorry, I just couldn't get over the last one.
No, but the shrimp was delicious.
It was delicious.
How about a little something sweet?
You like it.
I love it!
Let's go eat.
Yay!
The cheese was a little salty.
That's for sure.
Soul Tiramisu, sir.
Oh!
I like the word "soul" in there.
Soul Tiramisu!
Let's have a little tiramisu here, shall we?
Looks delicious.
Please come in.
The cup tiramisu specialty store that's all over social media.
Seoul Tiramisu!
Next, let's have a sweet Koriabla!
Let's have a sweet tiramisu here!
Abraita da Blue
Cute!
Cute.
No, this is not it.
Oh, really.
Mine is Oreo, isn't it?
Mine is matcha.
Yes, strawberry.Yes, strawberry.
You mean strawberry tiramisu?
Yes, strawberry tiramisu is...
It's a cup size tiramisu that's perfect for eating and drinking.
We have three popular flavors.
Go for it!
Bon appétit!
Please go ahead and have it!
If you hesitate, you'll be eaten!
On the contrary, I'm afraid.
It's not that kind of world, is it?
Delicious! The cream is so rich!
It's so good!
It's so rich, but it's so fluffy.
I'm picky about my tea.
It's still dipped in the fussy tea.
Delicious!
Delicious.
Oh, nice.
Matcha. It's authentic.
I can't get enough of this korea bra.
How is it that you Koreans can keep discovering
I wonder how you Koreans can discover all these delicious things one after another.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Oh, it's so good!
Also, I love the size of this one.
And it's easy to eat.
It's perfect for eating while walking around.
Show us your best Evisu bread, Poco!Show us your best Evisuppan, Poco.
Yes, I want to see the two of you in Evisuppan.
Poco.
Oh, that's good, Ponkichi.
Evisuppan.
Oh, yes, that's good.
What do you think? Inopy
Inopy is good, too.
Inopy.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, good.
Come on, come on, come on, master.
Bon appétit.
Yum.
Good, boring.
I've hit the bottom.
I'm going down quietly.
You'd better get some cream on your nose, you two.
Can you do it?
I got it.
Inopy.
You've got nose cream on your nose.
What are you talking about?
It's good, but it's really...
Oh, my God, it's so boring!
Why is it so boring?
Don't say that, you poor thing.
I'm sorry.Mmm.
Theamis, that was delicious.
It was delicious.
I put it on the inovi flowers.
It's so cute!
Now, here's the next restaurant!
Ta-da!
Mr. Heran!
Oh, my God, it's amazing!
The atmosphere of the media...
It's true.
There's a lot of media coverage.
This is a famous Japanese comedian, right?
No, I don't know him.
Yes, a top-class comedian.
So they've got a top-class comedian here.
That's what I meant.
In that sense.
I'd rather see Mr. Katori.
Hello.
Simiseherang is very popular for its original menu with a unique twist on Korean cuisine.
They have a famous Korean bra that's been loved for years.
Let's have a taste of Simi's kori abura!
Abragatabla
The taste of a famous restaurant at home Gif Eel Tamuro Goku
A famous eel restaurant with a long line of customers
Mikawa Ishiki's eels are carefully grilled by skilled artisans, the finest eels are grilled on the skin
2 eels for gift from 8,800 yen 2 eels for home from 7,760 yen
Now, grilled ayu (sweetfish) from Eel and Tamuro comes with the gift!Now it comes with grilled ayu with eel and tamuro.
Enjoy the taste of the season!
For more information, please visit Eel Restaurant Tamuro.
Free Comic Thiebaud to the world of free reading
Clear Morning
Summer is the time
Easy to drink and tasty is
the best
Yummmm!
Summer is the best time to drink
Clear morning
When can I have this?
What is that?
Isn't that awesome? It's got the specs of a gaming machine!
Galaxy S23 Ultra here! The legendary gamer is here!
This is crazy! It's fast and it's smooth! I want it!
Share the best! Galaxy S23 Ultra Double Storage Campaign!
I put a little extra vantelin on my back and shoulders and the stuff goes right in and takes the pain right away.
This is great. When it comes to pain, Banterine is the answer.
I've been doing some research on the colon, and I know you've been having some trouble with your bowel movements.
That could be a problem with your colon. The drug Zygaard has a combination of density bacteria and medicinal properties that will help bring your colon back to normal.
We'll get started on that.
What's this dish called?
Cheese Kalbi.
Did a famous super comedian come here?
Mr. Yamazaki?
No, no, no, he's a different person.
What was he like?
He was a little noisy.It was a little noisy.
It was loud.
Not well received.
In a good way.
Bright.
Bad Reputation Among Reputations.
Sweet and spicy seasoned Japanese pork spare ribs
Slowly baked in the oven
The pan is covered with as much cheese as possible
The spare ribs are ready to be served!
Once cooked, they are dipped in the original barbecue sauce
And then the cheese goes on stage!
Diving in happy-lucky excitement
When the cheese melts into a melting trotter, it's ready to eat
Once you try it, like a half dragon drama
You'll be addicted to it!
I knew I'd have to put on gloves and eat it again.
Looks so good!
I like the idea of getting your hands a little dirty.
It's good.
Let's eat.
As it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Be careful, it's hot.
It's hot.
Hot, hot, hot.
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Oh, yeah.
Mmm.Hmm.
It's growing.
Mmm.
Delicious.
I love it.
The original sauce is so good!
The original sauce is a perfect match with the cheese.
You can enjoy the tangy and spicy taste later!
Looks delicious!
Yum!
Delicious! It's delicious after all!
It's good, Po-chan!
Po-chan!
No, it's great.
Po-chan, you're amazing.
There's too much cheese.
Po-Chi, you took too much cheese.
You're a greedy Po-Chi, aren't you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Greedy Pengy Pengy Pengy Pengy Pengy Pengy
But you know what, this cheese is already easy to eat.
It's easy to eat now.
You can eat just the cheese.
Yum!
I've never had spare ribs before.
Oh, yeah.
It's so fun and delicious!
Also, the meat tastes great around the bone.
Po-chan basically puts so much around the mouth!Poe, you basically put an awful lot of it around your mouth.
He doesn't seem to mind.
Gobble it up.
So this is Po-chan.
Let's do it!
I'll do it.
Watch your hair.
Oh, my hair.
Eunapie.
It's good.
It's a little tomato-y.
Maybe a little sour.
Yeah, it's good.
And the meat is really juicy.
Yes, it is.
Then, let's see your face!
Bo-chan, first of all...
Charge and go!
Excuse me, please hurry up!
Charged?
Sir?
You look tired.
Yes, sir.
QP core?
Alpha Charge.
Relieves fatigue and replenishes the body's nutritional needs.
You're not coming down?
QP Core Alpha Charge
Charge and go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
QP Core?QP Core?
Alpha Charge
For Relieving Fatigue
Alpha Charge?
Nutritional supplement
Alpha Charge
For fatigue
Charge!
Alpha Charge
Don't get ahead of yourself
Two couples on the same accommodation plan
However
For 2 persons per night in a double bed room
17,500 yen will be charged
Cheap!
I'm sorry, but you're getting a deal!
12,250 yen per night for two persons
What?
What's the discount?
Trivago.
Different sites have different rates for the same hotel.
Trivago makes it easy to find the best rates by comparing rates on popular reservation sites.
Try Trivago next time.
What?
Tritori Tritori.
Hotel Trivago, the flower-clad test of mange.
The lady behind the scenes pulling the strings And intersecting destinies heading to the end of the line
Collapsing Star Trail. Appearance rate increasing.
No! No large prawns to whet your summer appetite.
No more tzatziki! No more chicken bites!Zakchiki, Bite of Chicken...
Crunchy Summer never stops! New Crunchy Summer from Domino's
New Kamen Rider the Movie is already available exclusively on Prime Video
July 21
No extra charge for Prime members!
Does it start with a battle?
Dominant can use the power of the summoned beast that inhabits him.
Break everything!
Protect your knees before its unholy blood!
What we want, what we're trying to create...
A world where people can live as people.
Come on! Recruit!
Nexgard for the still-drinking! We made it tasty with your dog's best interest in mind!
Dog First Nexgard
Nexgard is available at veterinary clinics. This broadcast is brought to you courtesy of our sponsors.
Then, let's see Kyoichi's Ebisu face!
First of all, Po-chan!
Delicious!
Yes, Po-chan!
Yes!
Po-chan! Po-chan! Po-chan! Shrimp face!
No, I don't think so.
Po-chan! Po-chan! Po-chan!
No, I don't.
Next to the simple one, there's an Evisu.
I thought you were going to make an infinite number of Ebisu faces.
The family is more prominent.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Cute, cute little Yunopi Peepee.
Ebisu Ebisu in the middle of Ebisu.
Next to Meguro, it's EbisuAfter Meguro, it's Ebisu.
I always say that.
Outside and inside.
One more time and then we both eat.
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit.
Wow.
They're both so cute.
Ebi chu ebi chu ebi chu ebisu face.
Next to the middle one is an Ebisu.
That's Hibiya.
Tohyoko, you did it, didn't you?
Hibiya from far side
Hibiyaka to far-Yoko
There are people from all over the world.
So you can change trains?
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Thank you very much
I'd like to come.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go. Meguro no Kuni is in Ebisu.
Next time, the oil show begins.
Performance Oil
Even Kasuga-sama's body starts to dance
It's thick, thick, thick!
Original video streaming on Tver
Please look forward to the next episode!
Red Black New Sensation Fruity UCC
Hey, Otchin, come here, come here!
Come on, come on, come on!Pops, that's what I'm talking about.
Here we go. Ready, go!
So cute!
Red hot summer is here! Even hotter this year!
Try one hot! 1 hot!
3 hot! Hot!
5 hot! How hot can you go?
Challenge the spiciness! Red Hot Chicken!
Hot! Kentucky today!